<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Animalpedia</string>
    <string name="pilih_gambar">(Select image to open gallery)</string>
    <string name="daftar_ras_judul">Animal Race List</string>
    <string name="go_back">Back</string>
    <string name="tikus">Mouse</string>
    <string name="burung">Bird</string>
    <string name="tikus_list_title">Rat Race List</string>
    <string name="burung_list_title">Bird Race List</string>
    <string name="hiu">Shark</string>
    <string name="paus">Whale</string>
    <string name="paus_list_title">Whale Race List</string>
    <string name="hiu_list_title">Shark Race List</string>
    <string name="acomys_nama">Acomys</string>
    <string name="acomys_asal">Africa</string>
    <string name="acomys_deskripsi">Acomys is a genus of rodent species. Similar in appearance to the rats of the genus Mus, the genus is a small mammal with a pale tail.</string>
    <string name="tikus_ladang_bergaris_nama">Striped Field Rat</string>
    <string name="tikus_ladang_bergaris_asal">Eastern Europe to East Asia</string>
    <string name="tikus_ladang_bergaris_deskripsi">The striped field mouse (Apodemus agrarius) is a type of mouse in the family Muridae. The distribution of this species extends from Eastern Europe to East Asia.</string>
    <string name="tikus_rumput_sudan_nama">Sudan Grass Rat</string>
    <string name="tikus_rumput_sudan_asal">Africa Region</string>
    <string name="tikus_rumput_sudan_deskripsi">The Sudanese grass rat (Arvicanthis ansorgei) is a species of rat in the family Muridae. The species is found in Burkina Faso, Guinea-Bissau, Mali, Niger, Senegal, Benin, Ivory Coast, Ghana, Guinea and Togo.</string>
    <string name="gerbil_nama">Gerbil</string>
    <string name="gerbil_asal">North Africa</string>
    <string name="gerbil_deskripsi">Gerbils are a sub-family of the rodent family Muridae. Once referred to as the desert rat, the subfamily includes about 110 species of African, Indian and Asian rodents, including the sand and jird rat, all adapted to dry habitats.</string>
    <string name="tikus_hutan_nama">Forest Rat</string>
    <string name="tikus_hutan_asal">Europe</string>
    <string name="tikus_hutan_deskripsi">The forest rat (Apodemus sylvaticus) is a type of Muridae rat native to Europe and northwest Africa. The species is related to the yellow-necked mouse (Apodemus flavicollis) but differs in that it lacks yellow fur around the neck, has smaller ears, and is usually a smaller body: about 90 mm (3.54 in) long and 23 g in weight.</string>
    <string name="petromyscus_nama">Petromyscus</string>
    <string name="petromyscus_asal">West Africa</string>
    <string name="petromyscus_deskripsi">Petromyscus is a genus of rodents in the family Nesomyidae. So different from other rodents that it is placed as the only genus in the subfamily Petromyscinae.</string>
    <string name="beo_nama">parrot</string>
    <string name="beo_asal">Sri Lanka, India, Philippines and Lesser Sunda</string>
    <string name="beo_deskripsi">Parrots, mamiang, or gold tinong (Gracula) is a kind of bird member of the Sturnidae tribe (starlings and their relatives). Its natural distribution area is from Sri Lanka, India, the Himalayas, eastward to the Philippines, Java to the small Sunda islands. This bird can be found in the lowlands to highlands of more than 2000m.</string>
    <string name="cenderawasih_nama">Cenderawasih</string>
    <string name="cenderawasih_asal">Papua, Indonesia</string>
    <string name="cenderawasih_deskripsi">Birds of paradise are members of the family Paradisaeidae of the order Passeriformes. Cendrawasih is usually found in Indonesia such as in eastern Papua, Papua New Guinea, Torres strait islands, and eastern Australia. Birds of this family are known for the plumage of many male birds, especially the very elongated and intricate feathers that grow from their beaks, wings or heads.</string>
    <string name="burung_hantu_nama">Owl</string>
    <string name="burung_hantu_asal">Spread all over the world except Antarctica</string>
    <string name="burung_hantu_deskripsi">Owls are a group of birds that are members of the order Strigiformes. This bird belongs to the class of birds of prey (carnivores, meat eaters) and is a night animal (nocturnal). In all, there are about 222 known species, which are distributed worldwide except Antarctica, most of Greenland, and some remote islands.</string>
    <string name="burung_unta_nama">Ostrich</string>
    <string name="burung_unta_asal">North Africa and Arabia</string>
    <string name="burung_unta_deskripsi">The ostrich is the largest living bird. Up to 2.5 meters (8 ft) in height, it is large enough for a small adult to ride on them and has been used in parts of North Africa and Arabia as a race mount. This bird cannot fly and belongs to a lesser known primitive group, namely the ratites (Palaeognaths). Its scientific name is Struthio camelus.</string>
    <string name="kakatua_nama">Cockatoo</string>
    <string name="kakatua_asal">Indonesia</string>
    <string name="kakatua_deskripsi">Cockatoo (tribe Cacatuidae) is a type of ornamental bird that has beautiful feathers with a fairly loud shrill voice. This species is one of the birds with a pretty good intelligence, so it is often used for entertainment events at zoos or other entertainment places.</string>
    <string name="jalak_bali_nama">Bali Starling</string>
    <string name="jalak_bali_asal">Bali, Indonesia</string>
    <string name="jalak_bali_deskripsi">Bali starling (Leucopsar rothschildi) is a kind of medium-sized songbird, with a length of approximately 25cm,[1] from the Sturnidae tribe. He is also known as Curik Rather than Starling.[2] Bali starlings are only found in the forests of the western part of the island of Bali and are endemic to Indonesia.</string>
    <string name="paus_biru_nama">Blue Whale</string>
    <string name="paus_biru_asal">North Atlantic and North Pacific</string>
    <string name="paus_biru_deskripsi">The blue whale is considered to be the largest animal that has ever lived on Earth. They reach lengths of up to 100 feet and weigh from 100 to 150 tons. Their skin is a beautiful gray-blue color, often with light spots.</string>
    <string name="paus_bungkuk_nama">Humpback Whale</string>
    <string name="paus_bungkuk_asal">Montery Beach, California U.S</string>
    <string name="paus_bungkuk_deskripsi">The humpback whale is known as the great-winged New Englander because it has long pectoral fins, or pectoral fins, and is humpback. Its majestic tail and spectacular behavior make this whale a favorite of whale watchers. Humpbacks are medium-sized baleen whales with a thick layer of blubber.</string>
    <string name="paus_sikat_nama">North Atlantic Brush Whale</string>
    <string name="paus_sikat_asal">Atlantic Ocean</string>
    <string name="paus_sikat_deskripsi">The North Atlantic brush whale is one of the most endangered marine mammals, with only about 400 remaining. Known as The Right Whale for hunting whales because of its slow speed, tendency to float when killed, and its thick layer of fat.</string>
    <string name="paus_bryde_nama">Whale Bryde</string>
    <string name="paus_bryde_asal">Tropical Waters</string>
    <string name="paus_bryde_deskripsi">Bryde\'s whale (pronounced broodus) is named for Johan Bryde, who built South Africa\'s first whaling station. They are 40 to 55 feet long and weigh up to 45 tons and are most commonly found in tropical and subtropical waters.</string>
    <string name="paus_beluga_nama">Beluga Whale</string>
    <string name="paus_beluga_asal">The North Pole</string>
    <string name="paus_beluga_deskripsi">Beluga whales are called sea canaries by sailors because of their distinctive vocalizations, which can sometimes be heard through the hulls of ships. The all-white color of the beluga and round forehead make it different from other species. It is a toothed whale that finds its prey using echolocation.</string>
    <string name="paus_sirip_nama">Fin Whale</string>
    <string name="paus_sirip_asal">North Atlantic and Antarctica</string>
    <string name="paus_sirip_deskripsi">The fin whale or fin whale (Balaenoptera physalus) is a marine mammal that belongs to the suborder of baleen whales. The whale, which measures almost 27 meters in length,[1] is the second largest whale and the second largest animal in the world after the blue whale.</string>
    <string name="hiu_biru_nama">Blue Shark</string>
    <string name="hiu_biru_asal">Tropical and Sub-Tropical Ocean</string>
    <string name="hiu_biru_deskripsi">The blue shark or great blue shark (Prionace glauca) is a species of shark in the family Carcharhinidae, which inhabits tropical and subtropical oceans around the world. This shark likes colder water[3] and is able to travel as far as New England to South America. The blue shark is classified as a near threatened species by the IUCN.</string>
    <string name="hiu_martil_nama">Hammerhead Shark</string>
    <string name="hiu_martil_asal">Warm Waters</string>
    <string name="hiu_martil_deskripsi">The hammerhead shark or in English called the Hammerhead Shark has a head shape resembling a flat hammer with eyes and nostrils at the end of the head. The unique shape of his head makes him able to maneuver in water with high accuracy.</string>
    <string name="hiu_gergaji_nama">Saw Shark</string>
    <string name="hiu_gergaji_asal">Australia, India, South Africa</string>
    <string name="hiu_gergaji_deskripsi">The saw shark or Saw Shark has a long, blade-like snout that is equipped with a series of teeth like a double-edged saw. This fish is similar to saw rays, but differs in the location of the gill slits.</string>
    <string name="hiu_threser_nama">Thresher Shark</string>
    <string name="hiu_threser_asal">Indo-Pacific and the China Sea</string>
    <string name="hiu_threser_deskripsi">The thresher shark consists of four species, all four of which are characterized by a tail on the upper fin that is up to 50 percent of the total length. This shark has a short snout and large eyes in front of the head. The second dorsal fin is much shorter than the first.</string>
    <string name="hiu_zebra_nama">Zebra Shark</string>
    <string name="hiu_zebra_asal">Pacific-Indonesia</string>
    <string name="hiu_zebra_deskripsi">The Zebra Shark, Stegostoma fasciatum, is a shark in the Indo-Pacific waters that has very long fins, almost as long as its body. This shark is given the name Zebra shark because of the stripes on its body that are similar to zebra stripes.</string>
    <string name="hiu_greenland_nama">Greenland Shark</string>
    <string name="hiu_greenland_asal">Greenland</string>
    <string name="hiu_greenland_deskripsi">The greenland shark (Somniosus microcephalus) is a slow swimmer. The swimming speed of the shark that lives in the cold waters around Greenland and Iceland is only 2.7 km per hour. According to scientists, this condition is due to the low temperature of the water in the Arctic Ocean.</string>
    <string name="profil">Eki Alfani</string>
    <string name="identitas_lengkap">full identity</string>
    <string name="nama">Name :</string>
    <string name="nim">NIM :</string>
    <string name="nim_value">" 200602103"</string>
    <string name="prodi">Major :</string>
    <string name="prodi_value">" Informatics Engineering"</string>
    <string name="kelas">Class :</string>
    <string name="kelas_value">" D"</string>
    <string name="tugas">Task :</string>
    <string name="tugas_value">" Mobile Programming"</string>
    <string name="hobi">Hobby :</string>
    <string name="hobi_value">" Fishing"</string>
    <string name="btn_profil">Profile</string>
    <string name="judul_profil">Student Profile</string>
    <string name="nama_value">" Eki Alfani"</string>
</resources>